{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application."
    },
    {
      "name": "sdfasdfasdfa",
      "description": "asdfasdfasf",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "asdf",
      "description": "asdfa",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "back": "asdf",
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdfasf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "back": "asdfasf",
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "werqwer",
      "back": "werqwer",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "qwerqwer",
      "back": "qwerqwer",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfadf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfaf",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfas",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfaf",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "adfasfd",
      "back": "asdfasdf",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 25
    }
  ]
}